JOHAN DENNING

PRODUCT- AND PEOPLE LEADER

PROFILE

I am a skilled product- and people leader with experience in managing highly agile cross-functional teams.

I believe that if we want to make sustainable changes, we need to always ask questions that challenge the ordinary.

I believe that centering energy and creating harmonious teams is what creates meaningful and successful impact.

And I believe that it's only through deep empathy that we can make impact that matters.

SKILLS

- Leadership
- Agile management
- Strategy and innovation
- Agile process expert
- · Design thinking/methodology
- Data analysis
- Qualitative research lead

HOW TO REACH ME

Phone: +45 61330977

Email: johan.denning@gmail.com Address: Sønderbyvej 37, 6091 Bjert

RELEVANT CAREER SUMMARY

MoneyFlow

Product Manager, March 2021 - March 2023

- · Leading a product team
- Mentoring and coaching individuals and the team
- Establishing and leading an empowered team culture
- · Company and product strategy
- Leading project and product iterations from idea to deployment
- Data- and research-driven prioritization

Play Magnus Group

Head of Product, Sep 2020 - March 2021

- · Launching a SaaS platform from ground-up
- Managing and leading 5 cross-functional leaders with a total of 17 employees
- Leading strategy and innovation
- Owning the full product
- Managing qualitative and quantitative research processes on an organizational and group level

General Manager, Oct 2019 - March 2021

- Established a new subsidiary and IT team
- Running daily operations for a team of 12 employees
- Built a successful SaaS product from ground-up
- · Established an agile mentality and workflow
- Established a culture of responsibility and design thinking

EDUCATION

Master

• Cand.mag. in Applied Cultural Analysis

Bachelor

· Bachelor Degree in European Ethnology

Upper Secondary

• Stx - advanced German, English, History, Danish

REFERENCES

"Johan did a wonderful job in setting up an office in Riga and creating a development team from scratch. He is easy to work with, a strong people manager, and very dependable. Johan personally commits to achieve the goals, takes 'responsibilities' very seriously, and steps up when the situation requires it."

Pieter Geeraerts - CEO, Play Magnus Group.

"I have been working alongside Johan for more than a year and I must say he is one of the best leaders you can get. He managed to build a solid team around himself, connecting diverse people and creating a highly performant work atmosphere"

> Vladimirs Mihnovics - Tech Lead, Play Magnus Group

"Johan's deep knowledge in the field of user research and ability to deliver spot-on insights makes him a remarkable communicator and design researcher. Johan works with professional pride and a level of communicative skill I have never known."

Kasper Wejse - former partner, Nava

HOW TO REACH ME

Phone: +45 61330977

Email: johan.denning@gmail.com Address: Sønderbyvej 37, 6091 Bjert

Product Manager, Jun 2019 - Oct 2019

- Owning the full product
- Managing a development team on the principles of design thinking and empowerment
- Sprint planning
- · Design workshop
- Design methodology
- · Product service design

Product Manager, Gambyt, Dec 2019 - Dec 2020

- Responsible for innovating and bringing a new product to market
- Leading a small innovation and dev team
- Leading research
- Service design
- Workshops

Nava Culture Consultancy

Co-Founder & Researcher, Jan 2017 - Jan 2019

- Led a research campaign in collaboration with the Danish Business Authority
- Executed qualitative interviews on a national level
- · Research design
- Turning data into valuable customer insights
- Collaborating in cross-functional teams

OTHER PROJECTS

Design Researcher, Local Currency, Jan 17 - May 17

- Planning and scoping research
- Executing research
- · Research design
- Analysis
- Turning data into valuable customer insights

Design Researcher, Schulze+Grassov, Sep 16 - Oct 16

- · Planning and scoping research
- Executing research
- Research design
- Analysis
- Turning data into valuable customer insights

OTHER EXPERIENCES

Founder & Creative Director, History Alive, Jun 15 - Sep 16

- Running a small start-up project making audiowalks for history and culture
- Scriptwriting
- Audio production
- Commercial experience
- Sales experience